

My name is Vincent and I work as a freelancing web designer and developer in Stockholm, Sweden.

Design and technology has always been my main interests and with both these passions web designer is a great combination! After studying system development and computer science I've been freelancing. I've also worked at and with some different agencies with both small and some very big clients.

When I'm not working with clients I like to work on side projects and open-source tools to keep the creativity and mind going.

VINCENT ORBACK

vorback@gmail.com | +46 725 309 222 | vincentorback.se

Experience

Web designer and developer Freelancing

2012 - Now

Daytona Communications Front-end developer

Oct 2013 - Jun 2015

Front-end developer Queensbridge

Mar - Sep 2013

Traffic Light Developer (internship)

Dec 2012

Education

Malmö University Computer Science

2011 - 2012, Malmö, Sweden System development Web development 1 Web development 2

Motion pictures

Södertörn University English A

2011, Stockholm, Sweden

Riddarfjärdens Gymnasium Graphic design & journalism

2011, Stockholm, Sweden